[{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664607571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":13958,"timeElapsed":630014},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664626306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":18732,"timeElapsed":648749},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664645093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":18784,"timeElapsed":667536},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664651906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6811,"timeElapsed":674349},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":11324,"timeElapsed":685676},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664684838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":21603,"timeElapsed":707281},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664691933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":7092,"timeElapsed":714376},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664698959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":7023,"timeElapsed":721402},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664705993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":7032,"timeElapsed":728436},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664715347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":7444,"timeElapsed":737789},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664718339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2990,"timeElapsed":740782},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664721817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3476,"timeElapsed":744260},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664724845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3025,"timeElapsed":747288},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664728535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3688,"timeElapsed":750978},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664732259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3721,"timeElapsed":754702},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664734067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":756510},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664737020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2950,"timeElapsed":759463},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664739109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":761552},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664747673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7569,"timeElapsed":770116},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664749942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":772385},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664753073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3130,"timeElapsed":775516},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664758196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":5121,"timeElapsed":780639},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664761338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3140,"timeElapsed":783781},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664765589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4249,"timeElapsed":788032},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664767420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1827,"timeElapsed":789862},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664770756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3334,"timeElapsed":793199},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664772301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1543,"timeElapsed":794744},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664784144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":10879,"timeElapsed":806587},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664789559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5413,"timeElapsed":812002},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664792546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2985,"timeElapsed":814989},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664796446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3898,"timeElapsed":818889},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664799861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3413,"timeElapsed":822304},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664806172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6308,"timeElapsed":828615},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664807733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1559,"timeElapsed":830176},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664815266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7531,"timeElapsed":837709},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664816908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1639,"timeElapsed":839351},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664827271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":9278,"timeElapsed":849714},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664829359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":851802},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664832087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2726,"timeElapsed":854530},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664833801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1711,"timeElapsed":856244},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664836177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2374,"timeElapsed":858620},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664840643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4464,"timeElapsed":863086},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664842926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2281,"timeElapsed":865369},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664845116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":867559},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664848023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2905,"timeElapsed":870466},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664861327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":11464,"timeElapsed":883770},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664863631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2302,"timeElapsed":886074},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664866957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3323,"timeElapsed":889400},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664870551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3592,"timeElapsed":892994},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664873282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2728,"timeElapsed":895725},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664879804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":902247},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664881861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":904304},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664887782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5919,"timeElapsed":910225},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664895653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7869,"timeElapsed":918096},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664905739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5766,"timeElapsed":928182},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664907306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1565,"timeElapsed":929749},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664909954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2646,"timeElapsed":932397},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664912068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":934511},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664914580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2510,"timeElapsed":937023},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664916996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2413,"timeElapsed":939439},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664918991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1993,"timeElapsed":941434},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664925063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6070,"timeElapsed":947506},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664933784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":8708,"timeElapsed":956227},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664944340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":8851,"timeElapsed":966783},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664945751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1409,"timeElapsed":968194},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664949016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":971459},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664959163,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10145,"timeElapsed":981606},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664962734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3569,"timeElapsed":985177},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664964957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":987400},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664970747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5787,"timeElapsed":993190},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664972496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1747,"timeElapsed":994939},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664975315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2817,"timeElapsed":997758},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664976877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1560,"timeElapsed":999319},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664984734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6796,"timeElapsed":1007177},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664986787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2051,"timeElapsed":1009230},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664989187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":1011630},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664991625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2436,"timeElapsed":1014068},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664993180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1553,"timeElapsed":1015623},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664997087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3905,"timeElapsed":1019530},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664998771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1681,"timeElapsed":1021214},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665001298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2525,"timeElapsed":1023741},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665004817,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3517,"timeElapsed":1027260},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665007591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2772,"timeElapsed":1030034},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665013888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5104,"timeElapsed":1036331},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665015565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1675,"timeElapsed":1038008},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665018212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2644,"timeElapsed":1040654},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665020163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1949,"timeElapsed":1042606},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1561,"timeElapsed":1044169},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665025618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3889,"timeElapsed":1048061},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665027112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1491,"timeElapsed":1049555},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665029152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2038,"timeElapsed":1051595},{"subjectID":"csha2gjc8v","prolificID":"5d8b66f5d189bd001a378273","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d0eceb8ccbc6ba80e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665031352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":1053795}]